http://en.rian.ru/docs/about/feedbackprivacy.html

To improve the performance of our website, show the most relevant news products and targeted advertising, we collect technical impersonal information about you, including through the tools of our partners. You can find a detailed description of how we use your data in our Privacy Policy. For a detailed description of the technologies, please see the Cookie and Automatic Logging Policy.
By clicking on the "Accept & Close" button, you provide your explicit consent to the processing of your data to achieve the above goal.
You can withdraw your consent using the method specified in the Privacy Policy.
Accept & CloseSputnik Internationalall editionsLog inRegisterLog out06:48 GMT11 December 2020
HomeWorldBusinessOpinionTechViralRadioMultimediaUKUSIndiaEuropeRussiaMiddle EastLatin AmericaAsia & PacificAfricaThe BackstoryBy Any Means NecessaryThe Critical HourFault LinesShooting from the LipThe Mother of All Talk ShowsPolitical MisfitsPhotoInfographicsCartoonsVideoPodcastsListen LiveSearchCOVID-19 global dataConfirmed cases:  Recoveries:  Deaths:  JHU CSSEFeedbackYour name*Your e-mail address*Text*Your message is sent.Please type your namePlease type your e-mailPlease type textWrong code
Please note that this feedback form is only used to contact us regarding the processing and protection of personal data. Requests not related to the protection of personal data will not be considered.
For requests not related to the protection of personal data, please use the address from the Agency contact list.
Processing of your personal data upon your request is carried out by our team to cooperate with you in resolving your issue.
By checking this box, you confirm that you have read, understood and accept the processing of your personal data and its legal basis.
* — required fieldsNewsLatestMost Read06:32
GMT
Yet Another Enigmatic Monolith, Covered With Mysterious 'Coordinates', Discovered in Australia06:27
GMT
'He Saved 2020': Fans Ecstatic as Kid Cudi Drops 'Man on the Moon III'06:10
GMT
Sweden to Remove 'Mother' and 'Father' From Parental Code to Make It Gender Neutral05:57
GMT
Death of Nine Infants Within 24 Hours at Indian Hospital Sparks Probe05:44
GMT
'Win-Win': National Interests to Outweigh Possible Outrage Over Morocco's Move to Recognise IsraelAll newsUK Health Watchdog Issues Warning After Two People Suffer Allergic Reaction to Pfizer VaccineUS Supreme Court Orders 4 States to Reply to Texas Election Lawsuit By 10 DecemberSeventeen US States Back Texas Bid To Overturn Biden ElectionAs Amount of Converts to Islam in Israel Rises, Jewish Organisation Vows to Show Them 'A Way Out'The Great Plane Robbery: Thieves Steal Radio Equipment From Russian 'Doomsday' PlaneAll newsMultimediaPhotoCartoonsInfographicsPatient Zero: Wuhan One Year After Coronavirus OutbreakFact Checker’s DelightUAE, Bahrain and Israel: Peace or Discord?
E-mail:Screen Name:Password:Confirm password:Log inPrivacy Policy
By checking this box, you provide your explicit consent to the processing of your personal data to create an account on the Sputnik website for posting comments to news. You can find a detailed description of how we use your data in our Privacy Policy.
You can withdraw your consent by using the feedback form or the method specified in the Privacy Policy.
Register* All fields are required
Please confirm your e-mail to continue. Confirmation instructions have been sent to
OkEnter e-mailPlease type the codeRestoreLog inPrivacy Policy
Success! Instructions to recover your password have been sent to
OkDo you have a Sputniknews.com account?YesNo
Hello, !
E-mail:Password:Remember meSign inI do not have a Sputniknews.com accountRegisterForgot your password?Privacy PolicyOk
Hello, !
E-mail:Screen Name:NextLog inI have a Sputniknews.com account
I agree to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of creating a personal account on this site using social media plugins, in compliance with the Privacy Policy
OkAre you sure you want to delete your Sputniknews.com account?YesNoYour account has been deleted! You can restore your account within 30 days by following the link sent to the e-mail address you entered during registration.Close
Hello,
!
We are committed to protecting your personal information and we have updated our Privacy Policy to comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), a new EU regulation that went into effect on May 25, 2018.
Please review our Privacy Policy. It contains details about the types of data we collect, how we use it, and your data protection rights.
Since you already shared your personal data with us when you created your personal account, to continue using it, please check the box below:
I agree to the processing of my personal data for the purpose of creating a personal account on this site, in compliance with the Privacy Policy.
If you do not want us to continue processing your data, please click here to delete your account.
If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at: privacy@sputniknews.com.
Next
Votre message a été envoyé!
E-mail:Password:Remember meSign inRegisterForgot your password?Privacy PolicyOther ways to sign in:Log in with FacebookLog in with VKSign in with GoogleOkSputnik push notifications
Get push notifications from Sputnik International
AcceptRefuse
